Guide to the McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Vertical File, 1948-1991
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Marketing Series (MKT), 20 Boxes
  - MKT 50. MARKETING RESEARCH
    - MKT 50:6 Ethics in Marketing Research; guidelines for "good" research; standards of practice
      See also: ADM 0:2-10.32, Social and Ethical Responsibilities, Corporate; ADV 25, DECEPTION, ETHICS, TRUTH AND TASTE IN ADVERTISING, all subsections; MKT 5:2-10, Social/Ethical Responsibility Concept; IOP 10:2-3, Global Challenges to Advertising; MKT 35:3, Consumerism; MKT 40:1-5, Market Research Management; in addition, see ADV 50:5-5.10.6, Suggested Standards/Disclosure Forms for Media Research, and ADV 25:4-1, Advertising Codes of Ethics
    - MKT 50:7 Sources of Information, in combination or N.E.C.
      See: content note at the beginning of the Marketing Series.
      - 50:7-1 Techniques of Information Gathering
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.2.6, Information Systems and Retrieval; MKT 40:5, Marketing Intelligence and Information Systems and subsections; SAL 10:5-2, Call Reports/Reporting, for information on sales force feedback
      - 50:7-2 Bibliographies, Book Lists, including books on advertising, and reference works, N.E.C. (Box 71)
      - 50:7-3 Catalogs and Guides to Marketing Films
      - 50:7-4 Informational and Statistical Programs of the U.S. Government
      - 50:7-5 Marketing and Industrial Directories
      - 50:7-6 Marketing and Industrial Maps
  - MKT 55. PRICING
    - MKT 55:1 Pricing Policies, Practices and Theories, N.E.C.
      See also: MKT 60:2-4, Product Development and Introduction; Marketing, Pricing and Marketing Budgets
    - MKT 55:2 Administered Pricing
    - MKT 55:3 Price Cutting (Price Wars)
    - MKT 55:4 Price Discrimination
    - MKT 55:5 Price Raising
    - MKT 55:6 Pricing Under Conditions of Economic Uncertainty
  - MKT 60. PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT AND INTRODUCTION
    - MKT 60:1 Development and Management
      - 60:1-1 Product Innovation, Development, Planning and Management, N.E.C.
      - 60:1-1 Product Innovation, Development, Planning and Management, N.E.C. (Box 72-73)
        See also: ADM 0:2-9, Planning, Corporate; ADM 0:2-7.5, Creative Techniques and Creativity
      - 60:1-2 Venture Team Approach (corporate venturing)
      - 60:1-3 Diversification/Product Differentiation
    - MKT 60:2 Marketing
      - 60:2-1 Marketing Strategy, N.E.C. (includes information on naming new products)
        See also: ADV 35:3-7, Introducing a New Product with Direct Mail
        - 60:2-1.1 DEMON (management model for marketing new products)
      - 60:2-2 Product Life Cycles
      - 60:2-3 Product Obsolescence, Deletion, Phase-Out
      - 60:2-4 Pricing and Marketing Budgets
        See also: MKT 55, PRICING, all subsections
      - 60:2-5 Sampling and Samples (not to be confused with sampling in marketing research; see MKT 50:2-1.35, Sampling)
      - 60:2-6 Test Marketing (includes concept testing)
      - 60:2-7 Promotion (includes advertising and concept advertising)
        See also: SAL 30, SALES PROMOTION, miscellaneous subsections; ADV 50:4-4, Copy: Copy/Message Testing and Research
  - MKT 65. PURCHASING PATTERNS
    See also SAL 40, SELLING TECHNIQUES, all subsections
    - MKT 65:1 Industrial Purchasing Practices and Procedures (how industry buys)
      - 65:1-1 The Industrial Buying Decision Process, N.E.C.
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.6, Decision-Making; MKT 40, MARKETING ADMINISTRATION, miscellaneous subsections, especially MKT 40:4, Decision-Making in Marketing, all subsections
      - 65:1-2 Buyer Behavior and Motivation, N.E.C. (Box 74)
        - 65:1-2.1 Emotional Aspects
      - 65:1-3 Identifying and Covering Buying Influences (number of buying influences in a company)
        See also: ADV 50:5-4.11, Circulation: Reach and Frequency, for information indicating that business publications reach buying influences not covered by salespeople
    - MKT 65:2 Purchasing Agents/Managers/Departments, N.E.C.
      - 65:2-1 Purchasing Power of Buying Influences
    - MKT 65:3 Purchasing Committees/Groups
    - MKT 65:4 Reciprocity/Trade Relations (selling's buddy system)
    - MKT 65:5 Sources of Information of Purchasing Influences
      See also: ADV 35:1-2, Business Papers vis-a-vis Other Media, all subsections; ADV 50:5-4.11, Circulation: Reach and Frequency
    - MKT 65:6 Value Analysis
    - MKT 65:7 Consumer Buying Attitudes, Behavior, Decisions, Motivations, N.E.C.
      See also: ADV 35:5, Media Communications Effectiveness
      - 65:7-1 Sources of Information of Consumer Purchasers
      - 65:7-2 Consumer/Buyer Attitudes Towards Other Countries' Products (includes information on foreigners' views of U.S. products or other countries' products)
  - MKT 70. THE GOVERNMENT MARKET
    - MKT 70:1 Guidelines for Dealing with Federal/State/Municipal Buying Agencies
      See also: MKT 70:2, Military Marketing
      - 70:1-1 U.S. Government Purchasing, Specifications and Sales Directories
    - MKT 70:2 Military Marketing: The Defense Procurement System: dimensions of the market and guidelines for selling in it
      - 70:2-1 Renegotiation
        - 70:2-1.1 Advertising to the Military
          See also: ADV 50:4.3.22, Copy: Approaches and Themes, Military
        - 70:2-1.2 The U.S. Government as an Advertiser
    - MKT 70:3 Surplus Property Buying/Marketing
    - MKT 70:4 Military/Industrial Marketing Differences
  - MKT 75. PACKAGING AS A MARKETING MECHANISM (Box 75)
  - MKT 80. TRADE ASSOCIATIONS
- Sales Series (SAL), 7 Boxes
  The subjects listed in this section are, very often, sales-oriented derivations of those to be found in general administration, so careful attention must be paid by information-seekers to the many see also references; for example, the classification SAL 35 deals with the problems of sales recruiting, selection and training, yet these sales problems are but part of the far greater subject, Personnel Management and Relations which, as the reference notes, is treated in great detail within the classification ADM 0:2-8. Similarly, SAL 25 concentrates on sales meetings but ADM 0:2-7.2.5 and subsections referenced explore the much larger topic of Conferences, Conventions, Seminars and Meetings and much of the documentation filed there could be of great value in expanding the generally narrow concept of a sales meeting. Researchers are advised to always check see also references.
  - SAL 0. THE FUNCTION OF SELLING IN MODERN MARKETING
  - SAL 5. THE SALES PROFESSION: The Salesperson's Role in Marketing, Careers in, and Education for, Selling (includes information on pros and cons of the professionalization of salespeople)
    See also: MKT 40:3, Marketing Communications Careers, Education, Recruitment, Training and Development, all subsections; SAL 35, SALES RECRUITING, SELECTION AND TRAINING, all subsections
    - SAL 5:1 Characteristics of a Good Salesperson (the qualities that make an ideal salesperson
      See also: SAL 40, SELLING TECHNIQUES, all subsections
    - SAL 5:2 Ethics in Selling
      See also: ADM 0:2-10.32, Social and Ethical Responsibilities, Corporate; ADV 25, DECEPTION, ETHICS, TRUTH AND TASTE IN ADVERTISING, all subsections; MKT 5:2-10, Social/Ethical Responsibility Concept; MKT 50:6, Ethics in Marketing Research
    - SAL 5:3 Ethnics/Minorities in Selling
      See also: ADM 0:2-7.8, Ethnics/Minorities in Management; MKT 40:3-1.1, Ethnics/Minorities in Marketing; MKT 40:3-2.1, Ethnics/Minorities in Communications; see SAL 5:5 for references to media salespersons
    - SAL 5:4 Women in Selling
      See also: ADM 0:2-7.28, Women in Management; MKT 40:3-1.2, Women in Marketing; MKT 40:3-2.2, Women in Communications; see SAL 5:5 for references to media salespersons
    - SAL 5:5 Media Salespersons
      See also preceding classifications for references to Ethnics/Minorities in Selling, and Women in Selling; this classification includes media salesperson information, whether or not that person is male or female or black or white. Includes information on media kits and media presentations as well as managing advertising salespeople. See also: ADV 50:5-5.10, Media-Sponsored Research/Promotion, all subsections; SAL 40:12, Sales Presentations, for additional information on this particular topic; SAL 40, SELLING TECHNIQUES, all subsections
    - SAL 5:6 Self-Development
      - 5:6-1 General Characteristics, N.E.C.
      - 5:6-2 Appearance (Box 76)
      - 5:6-3 Business Etiquette and Manners
      - 5:6-4 Health
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.7, Health: alcoholism, drugs, stress, burnout, etc.
      - 5:6-5 Management and Control of Time (includes information on time and territorial management in combination)
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.4.3, Time Conservation
      - 5:6-6 Memory Training
      - 5:6-7 Reading and Writing (includes information on written sales proposals)
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.2.9, Reading; ADM 0:2-7.2.13, Writing; MKT 50:4, Research Report Writing; SAL 10:5-2, Call Reports/Reporting
      - 5:6-8 Speaking, Listening and Vocabulary Building
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.2.8, Listening, and subsections; ADM 0:2-7.2.10, Speaking; ADM 0:2-7.2.7, Language Usage
      - 5:6-9 Spouses
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.22, Spouses
      - 5:6-10 Statistical Profiles (includes information on such topics as average age, time in selling, compensation levels, cost-per-call, sales expenses, etc., in combination)
        See also: specific subject headings for well-defined topics, e.g., Cost-per-Call
  - SAL 10. SALES MANAGEMENT
    - SAL 10:1 Duties, Functions, Skills, Profiles: the Sales Managers' Job
      See also: next subsection for information specifically oriented towards field sales management
    - SAL 10:2 Field Sales Management
    - SAL 10:3 Sales Management Training
      See also: SAL 35, SALES RECRUITING, SELECTION AND TRAINING, all subsections; ADM 0:2-8.21, Training and Development, N.E.C., and all subsections
    - SAL 10:4 Sales Departments: Organization and Structure, N.E.C.
      - 10:4-1 Auxiliary and Second Sales Forces, N.E.C. (includes information on leasing sales people)
      - 10:4-2 Inside Sales Forces
      - 10:4-3 Optimizing the Size of the Sales Force (includes information on the debate: more advertising expenditures or more sales staff?)
      - 10:4-4 Resident Sales People
    - SAL 10:5 Sales Control, N.E.C.
      - 10:5-1 Accounts/Calls/Lines/Products Handled
        See also: SAL 20:4-3, Cost-Per-Sales-Call; SAL 20:4-3.1, Cost to Close a Sale, which includes information on the number of calls required to make a sale
        - 10:5-1.1 Sales Call Planning
      - 10:5-2 Call Reports/Reporting (includes information on sales force feedback)
        See also: MKT 40:5, Marketing Intelligence and Information Systems, and all subsections; SAL 5:6-7, Reading and Writing, and references
      - 10:5-3 Measuring Sales Performance
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.14, Performance Appraisal; MKT 50:2-4, Market Analysis and Sales Forecasting, all subsections
      - 10:5-4 Quotas (Box 77)
        See also: MKT 50:2-4, Market Analysis and Sales Forecasting, all subsections
      - 10:5-5 Territories
        See SAL 5:6-5, Management and Control of Time, for information on time and territorial management in combination; see also: MKT 50:2-4, Market Analysis and Sales Forecasting, all subsections
  - SAL 15. MANAGER/SALES FORCE RELATIONS
    See also: ADM 0:2-8, Personnel Management and Relations, selected subsections; ADM 0:2-7.11, Human Values in Management: Human Relations; Manager-Manager Relations/Manager-Subordinate Relations
    - SAL 15:1 General Characteristics of Sales Manager-Subordinate Relations
    - SAL 15:2 Communications
      See also: ADM 0:2-7.2, Communications - Manager/Manager and Manager/Subordinate, Personal - Techniques, N.E.C., and all subsections; ADM 0:2-10, Public Affairs/Relations, all subsections for information on organizational - corporate - communication
    - SAL 15:3 Job Satisfaction in the Sales Force
      See also: ADM 0:2-8.10, Job Enrichment
    - SAL 15:4 Making Calls with the Staff
      See also: SAL 10:5-1, Accounts/Calls/Lines/ Products Handled; SAL 10:5-1.1, Sales Call Planning, and all references listed
    - SAL 15:5 Motivating the Staff: General Philosophies of Sales Motivation, N.E.C. (includes information dealing with several aspects of motivation)
      See also: ADM 0:2-8.12, Motivating Employees, and subsections; SAL 20:2, 20:3, and 20:3-1, Compensation, Sales Functions; SAL 35:2, Sales Training and Development
      - 15:5-1 Incentives: Plans/Programs, N.E.C.
        - 15:5-1.1 Sales & Marketing Management, special sections only on incentives
          Does not include occasional S M & M feature articles on incentives; for these, see preceding subsection.
      - 15:5-2 Incentive Travel
      - 15:5-3 Contests
      - 15:5-4 Non-Financial Incentives (commentary of a general nature on the theme, money is not the only answer)
      - 15:5-5 Problem Staffers
      - 15:5-6 Staff Turnover
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.21.13, Turnover, N.E.C., for general information on why people leave jobs, and subsection for information on executive mobility; ADV 50:5-4.15, Circulation: Turnover
  - SAL 20. SALES COSTS
    See especially, SAL 20:4-1, Sales & Marketing Management's annual surveys of selling costs
    - SAL 20:1 Sales Budgets
    - SAL 20:2 Compensation, Sales Executives and Managers
      See also: ADM 0:2-8.4, Compensation: Executive/Management, and all subsections; ADV 5:10-9, Advertising Agencies, Salaries; MKT 40:1-8, Marketing Communications Functions, Compensation.
    - SAL 20:3 Compensation, Salespersons, N.E.C.
    - SAL 20:3 Compensation, Salespersons, N.E.C. (Box 78)
      See also: ADM 0:2-8.4, Compensation: Executive/Management, and all subsections; ADV 5:10-9, Advertising Agencies, Salaries; MKT 40:1-8, Marketing Communications Functions, Compensation
      - 20:3-1 Dartnell Corporation's Biennial Sales Force Compensation Surveys
    - SAL 20:4 Cost Control, General Commentary, N.E.C.
      - 20:4-1 Sales & Marketing Management's Annual Survey of Selling Costs
      - 20:4-2 Sales Manpower Foundation - Sales Executives Club of New York - surveys of the cost of selling: historic
      - 20:4-3 Cost Per Sales Call
        See also: ADV 40:2-5, Advertising and the Cost of Selling, and subsections
        - 20:4-3.1 Cost to Close a Sale
          See also: preceding subsection, and SAL 10:5-1, Accounts/Calls/Lines/Products Handled
      - 20:4-4 Selling Expenses (T&E, etc.), N.E.C.
        - 20:4-4.1 Vehicle Expenses (fleet cars and management)
  - SAL 25. SALES MEETINGS
    See also: ADM 0:2-7.2.5 Conferences, Conventions, Seminars and Meetings, and all subsections
    - SAL 25:1 Planning, Staging, Conducting, and General Commentary on Sales Meetings, N.E.C.
    - SAL 25:1 Planning, Staging, Conducting, and General Commentary on Sales Meetings, N.E.C. (Box 79)
      - 25:1-1 Customer/Dealer Meetings
      - 25:1-2 Meeting Follow-Up
      - 25:1-3 Small Meetings
  - SAL 30. SALES PROMOTION
    - SAL 30:1 Promotion: Its Role in Marketing; Planning and General Commentary (includes information on the sales promotion vs. advertising debate)
      - 30:1-1 Promotion Expenditures: Marketing Communications annual reports
    - [Sales Promotion Management--see: MKT 40:1-7]
    - SAL 30:2 Selling Promotion to Top Management
    - SAL 30:3 Sales Promotion Aids: Premiums, Films, Incentives, etc.
      See also: SAL 15:5, Motivating the Staff, for additional information on incentives
      - 30:3-1 Sales Promotion Literature
    - SAL 30:4 Sales Promotion Audit/Measurement (evaluating the effects of company promotional activities)
  - SAL 35. SALES RECRUITING, SELECTION AND TRAINING
    See also: ADM 0:2-8, Personnel Management and Relations, all subsections, especially ADM 0:2-8.16, Recruitment, and ADM 0:2-8.21, Training and Development, all subsections; SAL 10:3, Sales Management Training
    - SAL 35:1 Recruiting/Selection
      Material which includes information on several segments of the recruiting/selection/hiring process. This material, in some instances, may also touch on the specifically isolated subjects which follow so it should always be examined when answering questions on these subjects.
      - 35:1-1 Aptitude/Psychological Testing
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.20, Testing
      - 35:1-2 Interviewing
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.9, Interviewing
      - 35:1-3 Job Descriptions
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.15, Position Descriptions/Job Posting
      - 35:1-4 Retirement
        See also: ADM 0:2-8.17, Retirement
    - SAL 35:2 Sales Training and Development
      Includes information on the role of sales trainers, instructional materials such as films and video tape, training philosophies and programs; see also: SAL 10:3, Sales Management Training; SAL: 15:5, Sales, Motivating the Staff, all subsections; SAL 25, SALES MEETINGS, all subsections; ADM 0:2-8.21, Personnel Management and Relations, Training and Development, all subsections; ADM 0:2-10.12, Films; Business, PR, and Sales
      - 35:2-1 Sales Manuals
  - SAL 40. SELLING TECHNIQUES (Box 80)
    See also: SAL 10:5, Sales Control, various subsections; SAL 15:4, Making Calls with the Staff; MKT 65, PURCHASING PATTERNS, all subsections, for information on the buying process.
    - SAL 40:1 Selling Techniques and Customer/Salesperson Relationships, N.E.C.
    - SAL 40:2 Closing the Sale
    - SAL 40:3 Comparative Selling
    - SAL 40:4 Consultative Selling
    - SAL 40:5 Creative Selling (includes information on using imagination and ideas in selling)
      See also: ADM 0:2-7.5, General Management, Creative Techniques and Creativity; ADV 5:10-3, Advertising Agencies, Creative Staff, N.E.C.
    - SAL 40:6 Follow-Ups/Follow-Through
      See also: ADV 45:2-2, Inquiries, Advertiser Evaluation, Handling and Follow-Up Practices
    - SAL 40:7 Lost Sales
    - SAL 40:8 Low-Pressure Selling
    - SAL 40:9 National Accounts: Selling, Servicing, Managing
      - 40:9-1 Key Account and Major Customer Selling
    - SAL 40:10 Overcoming Complaints and Objections, and other sales resistances, N.E.C.
      - 40:10-1 Price Resistance
    - [Planning--see: SAL 10:5-1.1, Sales Call Planning]
    - SAL 40:11 Prospecting/New Business Development (Box 81)
      See also: ADV 45, INQUIRIES, all subsections, particularly ADV 45:2-2, Advertiser Evaluation, Handling and Follow-Up Practices
    - [Reciprocity--see: MKT 65:4, Reciprocity/Trade Relations, selling's buddy system]
    - SAL 40:12 Sales Presentations
      See also: SAL 5:5, Media Salespersons, for information on media kits and media sales presentations
    - SAL 40:13 Selective and Specialized Selling
    - SAL 40:14 Selling in an Abnormal Economy
      See also: ADV 0:3, Advertising in an Abnormal Economy, N.E.C., and subsections; MKT 45, MARKETING IN AN ABNORMAL ECONOMY
    - SAL 40:15 Service Selling
      See also: MKT 5:2-3, Customer Service Concept
    - SAL 40:16 Summertime Selling
      See also: ADV 50:2-5, Seasonal Advertising, N.E.C., and ADV 50:2-5.1, Summer Advertising
    - [Systems Selling--see: MKT 5:2-11, Systems Concept, and subsection]
    - SAL 40:17 Telemarketing
      See also: ADV 45:5-3, 800 Number; SAL 10:4-2, Inside Sales Forces
- Alphabetical, Topical, Keyword Index
  This index is designed as a finder catalog for topics covered in the Vertical File. It is recommended that users, once a topic of interest is located, refer back to the designated heading and read it thoroughly, noting descriptive information and see also references.
  A
  ABP/A.D. Little Evaluation of 1100 Research Studies: ADV 40:2-1.1
  ABP/Taylor Instrument Study (of the business paper reading environment): ADV 40:3-7.1
  ABP's Business Marketing Laboratory Study (the Ryan Study; the Syracuse Study): ADV 50:5-4.2.1
  AIA (now B/PAA), Media Data Form Commentary: ADV 50:5-3.1.1
  AID(C)A and IPSO in Advertising: ADV 50:4-3.1
  ANCOM (Andean Common Market): IOP 0:3-1
  ASEAN (Association of South East Asian Nations): IOP 0:3-3
  Abnormal Economy, advertising in: ADV 0:3
  Abnormal Economy, marketing in: MKT 45
  Abnormal Economy, selling in: SAL 40:14
  Accompanying Reading Matter, effects on an ad: ADV 50:7-3
  Account Executives, agency: ADV 5:10-2
  Account Switching: ADV 5:3-4
  Accountability, in management (results-oriented concept): ADM 0:2-7.1
  Accounts/Calls/Lines/Products Handled, salespersons: SAL 10:5-1
  Action Learning/Training Techniques: ADM 0:2-8.21.2
  Actuarial Tables, communications industry: MKT 40:3-2.3
  Administered Pricing: MKT 55:2
  ADVERTISING (all subjects; see ADV and subsections, also specific topics carried under keywords; for example, Appropriations, advertising; Management, advertising; Clutter in Advertising, etc.):
  Advertising as a Public Relations Tool: ADM 0:2-10.3
  Advertising, international concepts and techniques: IOP 10:2-4 (*)
  Advertising Volume/Expenditures: ADV 55 (*)
  ABP Suggested Guidelines for Reporting Ad Volume: ADV 55:1-1.4
  Business Publications: ADV 55:1 (*)
  Direct Mail: ADV 35:3-14
  General Magazines: ADV 55:2
  International: IOP 10:2-10 (*)
  Multi-Media: ADV 55:3 (*)
  Reference Sources: ADV 55:4-3
  Worldwide: IOP 10:2-10.1
  Advertorials/Special Sections: ADV 50:4-3.12.1
  ADVISOR Project: ADV 10:3-5
  Advocacy Advertising: ADV 50:4-3.2
  Affirmative Action/EEO/Discrimination: ADM 0:2-8.2
  Agencies, advertising: ADV 5 (*)
  A la Carte vs. Full Service, etc.: ADV 5:4-1
  Account Executives: ADV 5:10.2
  Administration: ADV 5:10.1
  Around the World: 4As directories: IOP 10:2-6.2
  Attorney's functions: ADV 5:6-1
  Audits: ADV 5:3-3
  Billings and Income (agency rankings): ADV 5:2-1
  Billings by Medium: ADV 5:2-2
  Business Paper Billings (top industrial agencies): ADV 5:2-3
  Business Paper Page Placement: ADV 5:2-3.1
  Client Agreements and Contracts: ADV 5:3-2
  Client Relationships: ADV 5:3 (*)
  Compensation: fees vs. commissions: ADV 5:5-1
  Cost of Operations (agency financial management): ADV 5:5-2
  Costs, collateral, etc.: ADV 5:5-2.2
  Creative Staff: ADV 5:10-3
  Direct Mail, ad agencies and: ADV 35:3-2
  Executive Staff: ADV 5:10-4
  Fees vs. Commissions: ADV 5:5-1
  Full Service vs. A la Carte, vs. Boutiques, etc.: ADV 5:4-1
  Industrial: ADV 5:1-1
  International: IOP 10:2-6 (*)
  Advertising Age's compilation of foreign agency income, reports and profiles: IOP 10:2-6.1
  Choosing an Associate Agency: IOP 10:2-6
  Legal Aspects: ADV 5:6 (*)
  Marketing Directors: ADV 5:10-5
  Media Relationships: ADV 5:7
  Media Staff (buyers, directors, planners): ADV 5:10-6
  Mergers: ADV 5:6-2
  Networks, Leagues, Associations, etc.: ADV 5:8
  New Business Development: ADV 5:9
  Performance Evaluation: ADV 5:3-3
  Personnel: ADV 5:10 (*)
  Presentations: ADV 5:9
  Public Financing (Going Public: agency stocks and profits): ADV 5:5-3
  Rankings: ADV 5:2-1
  Recruitment, Training and Development: ADV 5:10-7
  Research Staff: ADV 5:10-8
  Salaries: ADV 5:10-9
  Selection: ADV 5:11
  Selection, single vs. multiple agencies: ADV 5:11-1
  Self-Promotion: ADV 5:9
  Services and Departments: ADV 5:12 (*)
  Starting a New One: ADV 5:13
  Technical Staff: ADV 5:10-10
  Turnover (account switching): ADV 5:3-4
  Turnover (people switching): ADV 5:10-11
  What They Do; How They Do It (the agency business): ADV 5:1
  Agents/Representatives vs. Company Sales Force: MKT 20:10-3
  Airline (inflight) Magazines: ADV 35:4-6.2.1
  Alcoholism: ADM 0:2-8.7
  Allis-Chalmers Study: ADV 40:2-2
  Alternate Delivery: ADV 50:5-4.10.2
  Alternative Work Schedules: ADM 0:2-4.12.1.1
  American Competitive Enterprise System, N.E.C.: ADM 0:2-4.1
  American Marketing Association: Surveys of Marketing Research: MKT 50:1-3
  Anniversaries, corporate: ADM 0:2-10.4